Out in the garden, the tower's falling, loving the summertime, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, in a beautiful
It's a gift.
We're doing tonight. Anything that is, I'm going to see you. I can play as Perks.
Effing low-key, Cloudsack. What's up guys?
Hey guys, love you guys. Thank you for being here.
There are many places you can decide to be tonight and you chose to be here with me.
And for that, I appreciate you.
Little bit like it's concerned right now because I haven't seen tricks in a while
My little it I know he's gonna show up tonight. I'm I how are you?
I do too. I think he will be, I mean, it's like, you know, he hasn't really ventured far and he doesn't, I don't think he would like, I think he's just hidden around.
Thank you. You say, I, I, I think he's around. Babe, I think it's an R, an R. It just treats right here.
I mean, I called him and he's in the company once.
The cats are really good at hiding, and I will very shortly, but I have a feeling he's
We like those when our catnip treats the nor loves catnip. She gets very
affected by it
Let's fill up you. I don't know what you believe in but if you believe in anything
Just like say a prayer for tricks and he comes home safe, right?
There's only so many things in our control, you know, all we could be controls ourself
Now we're doing tonight. Hey, babe. Oh, you just had a little shake. You shook. Oh, that was good. That's good. Thank you cloud
Be comfy be comfy settle them we're gonna have fun tonight, huh?
Oh, baby.
There's like one thing I don't like out of people,
especially, I mean, the worst thing I think is like
too much pride, I guess that was Lucifer's problem.
Yeah, a little bit too much pride because Lucifer, I heard him meow outside
Lucifer didn't just want to be like a Lucifer wanted to be God and there's like a difference. It's like
Being like God is one thing that's trying to be
inspiring it's like, you know
But trying to be God
Sometimes people are too eager to put themselves in that position and it's like and that's when
The worst thing happens besides pride. It's smugness and I saw this like smugness tonight. That is like
Maybe stick it's kind of like this. It's a sound
That sound is that second a laugh
I don't know if you ever heard that kind of laugh before out of anybody you hear that laugh it's probably time to like
I hear this.
Ah!
Can you hear these kind of laughs?
There's like a time when you're human, it's time to like humble yourself a little bit
because we're not God.
We have maybe like a seed of it, a seed of God inside of us.
You know what it's like?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Ah!
You know what I'm talking about, I don't know if you know what I'm talking about.
But I hear these like nightmare sounds, they're like, they're like basically just demons.
I think at this point the demons have taken over when someone's like, when they're like
Well, yeah, you're on the right track there. You're on the right track and but the other one is like a female a female kind of laugh
Almost out they almost sound like the exact same versions of the same demon
Right, but all of my demons. Hey guys, I do extra systems on the daily
Well, I burn the frickin sense, which is like the yeah, do you know I'm talking about this? I don't know
I don't know if I'm making sense, but these are the sounds that I'll be like, okay well
it's you know, imagine the sounds they make when they're making love, I don't know if
I don't know, I lost my voice a little bit.
So I don't know if I'm doing them perfectly.
But that's how that kind of,
oh, okay, I won't do it anymore.
It's like, it takes too much out.
I don't want to lose my voice again.
But it's like, wow.
I didn't know that kind of evil.
I always learned things.
And I think the people that like,
there's people that like,
Gave me some tough love a little bit tough love
Was it ultimately because they hated me what happened what didn't happen what didn't happen
Sometimes it yeah
It didn't happen
It's like
Being taken from being take, you know, I just feeling being taken from and
Then just instead of getting anything back
In your face
Like or giving giving love
I don't know if I'm making sense. I don't know if I'm making sense, but I'm trying to describe it the best way I can
These demons
I don't know or the devil like the devil themselves, I don't know. I don't know what those those people are
It's a wrong crowd
It took me a long time, like I do.
I always was chasing acceptance from like cool kids.
But I'm just like, you know,
I should have been like just remembering the losers, like me.
People that is just like, you know.
It's not what, and you don't remember it,
that movie it, that's what they called themselves,
the losers, but they were like the winners actually.
I kind of feel like sometimes
Feel like I
Don't know
Try my best
You never saw it. You never saw Stephen King's it. I
Remember when I was like how about year was it 92 93?
You never saw it. That's like the best movie in the world
Because it was a mini series on like I think it was like on ABC or something like that. You never saw it
Well thing that is you're in for a treat because I want you to as a homework assignment. I want you to go watch it
IT okay, just it's just a simple it is well it
And I'll just give you like a little synopsis
You never saw it and now you're not going to
Okay, you're not gonna take my recommendation. You're not gonna do your homework not interested. Okay
You're going out of time out
You need a little time out sometimes you need to listen like that's a little bit of the arrogance coming through
I'm telling you from the bottom of my heart
This is something you need to
Have a look at is that I've ever millions of hours of life
You know like it and you know 10 10 20 minutes
Okay, but it just to say up now now and I'm
Take this take the 30 second or the five minute timeout
Go maybe look at a trailer for it go maybe because
When you assume you not only make an ass out of you
Be making ass out of me
And that's why it's spelled a s s you
M e
Like I try to explain things I'm like I like I said out but here's here's the thing. I said
Alexander
McQueen
Check out this movie called psycho
And you said I'm gonna watch that movie. I'm gonna watch that. I
Didn't have to tell him very much about he's like I'm gonna check that out. I
Don't know I'll check it out my uh, if he tells me to check out something. I'll watch the trailer at least
Sometimes, you know, there's a lot to watch out. There's a lot of options and
Think that is if you come up here saying
You're timed up for five minutes because of your arrogance and I just gave a lecture about arrogance
Smugness not interested now, you don't know what you're talking about. I wouldn't like that
Maybe
I'm not the teacher. Maybe you're the teacher. I'm the student maybe like the teacher can learn from the student once in a while
I think that is
Okay
Little smugness out there a little smug and I was like trying trying to explain
That makes my skin crawl the smugness
No, no
At least you can say oh look at the trailer or maybe have heard of that movie or something you don't have to say no
Like I don't know what I'm talking about listen I watch this movie
But I think I was probably 10 years old it kills it as a mini-series on ABC
And it is a life
Changing movie and Canadian comedy show
Felipe how are you?
Um, or Philippe, Philippe, I'm sorry.
They're one of my favorite restaurants my dad used to take me to, and I,
not only as a kid, they take us as a family, but, um...
Took me when I was living kind of far further away. We go meet downtown LA. It's right by Union Station
It's called Philippe's or Philippe's. Hey, what's up?
And it's where the invention of the of the French dip sandwich, you know, my favorite sandwich was lamb
I had the lamb sale. I swear to God. I had a lamb sandwich every time I went there
French dip lamb sandwich. I had a purple pickled egg
You get a piece of chocolate cream pie and lemonade
and it has sawed us on the floor, you like go up,
there's an old fashion looking waitress.
You know, I think the waitresses
has probably have worked there since the 1960s, you know?
They just had just always worked there
because they loved it.
And you go up and you wait in line, a big long line,
there's several of them.
You go to the counter, you order what you want,
and they'd give you a tray with your food on it,
you go sit on a bench with a bunch of other strangers.
People with sawdust on the floor and you eat like the best most delicious meal
And my dad liked the lamb sandwich too. We both that was basically we got the same exact thing and we loved the pickled egg
They have a purple pickled egg. It's probably like the most delicious thing you've tasted. I swear
And
Wow, I mean the memory is my dad, you know
So I think they've probably served that in heaven, but it's called Philippe's or
Philippe's. Let me show you a picture of it maybe.
Because on the outside we go and I go in the parking lot.
I go in my car and then I look and his car would pull in
and like it's time to go. Time to go to eat. Time to eat the best lunch in the world.
I'll show you what it looks like. It's been there since I think in the 1920s.
Dantana, Los Angeles. Okay. Here's this. Here's the sign
This is where I'd go this that way know we know this here we go
And now your name is built a little different but friendship sandwiches
You sit the counter behind there and there's that
Okay, I'm not no I think that is I said I have a homework assignment for you like I'm the teacher whatever what you're the teacher too
Okay, we're both teachers
But I say hey, I think there's something you might
Like or learn from that and you just said nope not interested
Well when okay pretend you're in school and the teacher says
I've been assignment for you check out war and peace or check out
you know, Charlotte's web or something.
And you go, I'm not interested.
You know, the teacher does, they give you an F
because that was an assignment.
You know, this is like Stephen King.
Well, you know, it's more than Stephen King,
like Stephen King, I don't like the Stephen King book.
It's like a huge, huge book.
And I've, you know, it's like a lot different from the movie
or the mini series, which is probably hundreds of writers.
And I don't know.
Nothing to do with me, but it has nothing to do with me. It has everything to do with me at the same time
It has everything to do with me
Okay
Just
By it, you know, you can just humor humor me and say I'll check it out instead of just shooting me down. I
Know I know I know you're your thing that is
Know isn't he a little negative Nelly guys is everybody else seen the movie and it's like
There's something in there
For everyone
There's something it's like good, you know, I don't know no no
I don't want to try the piece of prime rib. I don't like it looks weird looks like you know, no
I don't want to try it
Well, it's gonna be the best thing you ever tried, but no we'd go to bed without dinner then
Just just forget it just forget it he doesn't get it guys
You didn't get it lying is different than humoring me
It's like it's like I've been trying to explain my improv an improv
You never negate what the person says you never negate it that ruins the joke that he does he gets I don't know
You never negate like here's improv. You don't say no
So if you understood improv he wouldn't have said no because that's not a word an improv an improv you always agree and
Then you take it a step further and stuff like that right
Being a wet blanket or a douchebag is saying
No, I mean, okay, sure. I'll watch that. Oh, yeah. It's a be obviously you will humor and say that sounds interesting
That sounds interesting. I'm gonna read. I'm gonna watch that tomorrow. Did Alex watch psycho today?
Probably not
These like these a hey, that sounds fucking great. I can't wait to watch that. Yes. It's about lying. No
Okay, okay. I'm not gonna give you a hard time. I'm not gonna give you a hard time. All I'm saying is that
Negativity can be
You know, you know, if they if the improv been saying no and negating it. No one would laugh. They'd go. Oh, I
They go, oh, I
Don't know. I can't explain any better. They go. Oh, that's not a good. That's that's where they go awkward
You know, I don't know if I can explain it better. You had your coffee. Well, I got my coffee right here
I haven't had my coffee yet
How did the speaker go on?
The speaker just went on on the phone why how is the speaker playing for a message that is weird
I'm not gonna be calling that number
How the fuck why are you on my phone on my speakerphone? You just called me. I've never had that happen in my life
Heavens are opening up
I think they are. You know what that means? The clouds are clearing. Hey, how's that go?
I can see clearly now the rain has gone.
I can see all obstacles in my way.
Gone are the dark clouds that had me gone.
It's gonna be a bright, bright, sunshiney day.
Maybe listen to that song think that's doing it. We would look would you look up bright sunshiney day song?
No, I'm not interested. No
No, no, no
No, I don't even care about that. I don't care if you recommend it. What does your recommendation mean to me? Nothing?
That's the thing that is
Okay, okay, maybe he does maybe he doesn't get maybe maybe the sky maybe the clouds are clearing a little bit
Just open your mind a little bit
And look the word it is in the word little bit it's the word it is in there
Isn't that strange it's a good song
Who doesn't like that song? I mean who wouldn't like it? It's like a universally part of being human is like
can see clearly now the rain has gone. It's like universally understood so maybe
that's what I was trying to say. I was trying to say I've had enough nose and
not interested and I don't care what you have to say and I don't care about your
recommendation. Pretend we're at a bar and you've had your coffee and you've had
Then you know that and that's like you know, you wouldn't say you have you seen this movie?
No, tell me what it's about
What what are you waiting? Why do you think I would like it like or something? I'm just like I don't want it
I'm not interested. I don't want to hear I saw there's a clown in it. I don't like clowns or something
You know, I mean that's just like no
It's hurt my heart you like a viscerally
You might as well just put a dagger in my heart
with that answer.
I'm back. Yeah, I got, oh my gosh.
Let me put up the, let me put up the link for us.
And thing that is, I do love you. You know I love you.
Okay.
Oh, look at this.
Now, now he's being the defiantina.
The 58-year-old men say,
whatever, enroll their eyes.
There's a 58-year-old bald man in Canada with so much intelligence and everything say
Whatever whatever mom
What do you say that's your mom whenever you might say it's your mom when you he's fussy. He's being a brat
Can I talk to your mother I want to talk to your mother doing this
I think it's time to bring back spankings for adult men
Let me just talk to her. Okay
You can't be in the room. It's gonna be like a parent-teacher conference
When you come out, but when she comes out of the room, she's gonna have a look on her eye
thing that is
What did you say your teacher when she asked you or he asked you to do that and do an assignment and you said no
Think it is how are you ever getting to the medical school?
You know that what how are you doing in the fifth grade determines how you're gonna do in middle school
How are you gonna do in high school?
How are you doing college and medical school and you're gonna be a doctor?
Thing that is
Get over my knee
And don't you dare laugh stop laughing when I do this
You probably just gonna laugh
You know, he won't even humor the spanking. He'll be like, you know, he'll be like
Stop fucking smiling!
Ooh, if I was to smile when I was the I got the cheeseboard out, you know what would happen?
That cheeseboard's gonna be coming on ten times harder until I'm not smiling anymore
Not not not not advocating, you know doing that, but it's like I'm saying my mom was kind of old school
We had a I don't even think she ever had to use the cheeseboard just the
She had it in this in in sight and just the idea of that cheeseboard was enough
For me to behave. I don't think it was ever used on me once
I know. He doesn't care about music. Yeah, he doesn't care about singing.
I can't stop the voice track. I'm sorry.
Unfortunately, as part of my comedy act, I decided to
imitate a woman named Christine.
It was your grandma's slipper, right?
I can't.
Oh, I can stop cracking my voice.
Have you heard of Peter Brady?
When it's time to change, it's time to-
Peter, all right!
You never heard of that?
Oh, excuse me.
How does that song go?
I'm gonna get the lyrics of the song
and I'm gonna sing it when it's time to change.
So I think it's time for me to change.
Maybe it's time for all of us to change a little bit.
Okay?
How does the song go when it's time to change? It's by the Brady Bunches. It's a classic song
It goes
It goes like this
It goes and I'm not gonna my voice is not gonna crack. Okay. I'm gonna try not to make it crack except when I do the Peter Brady part
Cha-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na, cha-na-na-na-na-na,
cha-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na, cha-na-na-na-na-na,
autumn, oh my god, autumn turns to winter,
and then winter turns to spring.
It's not just the seasons, you know, it goes for everything.
clouds can turn to rain and then it just might snow you got to take a lesson
from mother nature and if you do you'll know when it's time to change it's time
to rearrange that's my Peter Brady part don't fight the tide come along for the
ride don't you see
When it's time to change you got to
Who you are into what you're gonna be the very bunch of a lot of good wisdom
Day by day, it's hard to see the changes
You've been through a little bit of living a little bit of growing it all adds up to you
Every boy's a man inside, a girl's a woman too.
And if you want to reach your destiny,
here's what you've got to do.
When it's time to change, then it's time to change.
Don't bite the tide, come along for the ride,
don't you see?
When it's time to change, you've got to rearrange.
Dear God.
Dear God
I'm sorry about that
Okay, get out of here out Pico out. You're not welcome here out
I'm not trying to crack my boy. It's just cracking you try to imitate Christine for a day. I lost in the first day
I tried it. I think I think I've damaged my vocal cords
Trying to do her voice
You have a good night. You have a good night, sir
Out! Out! Get out of here!
You're lucky I don't time you out.
Pico.
Are you even, are you even black?
Thank you, Burning Joy. I don't think he was moved black.
It's like, I'm sure like Pico Graham and Midnight are like these obese white people, right?
he was just saying hello and he says stop now and then he goes da da da da da da da da da da da
and that's how he says hello he's not even black just like salmon's not even black
they're just taking these characters it's it's pico rico it's just salmon under an alt
salmon go do your own show i i don't want to ever even if i ever hear that laugh again i might
Plug something in my ears. I'm done
You know what sometimes God gives people these voices to warn us away from them you can just tell their evil
It's like oh
It's we're supposed to be
viscerally
Disturbed by this way, but you know what?
But there seem to be flock to dude. I need serious help
Talking people making demon sounds as you're doing it projection much and smart leaving cat out. Mr. Abusive. I
Am socially awkward well, you're socially
Expelled for my chat permanently
And then I never have to hear your dumb comments again
YouTube is a funny place.
It sounds like a Sam-Man kind of,
Eh, eh, eh, eh, eh.
I'm not, I'm, these are actually their voices.
These are actually what they sound like.
I'm not making demon noises.
This is what they sound like.
Demons.
You get it?
Yeah.
I mean, gorillas have nicer voices.
I mean, like not, and I'm not saying,
but they go, oh, like, you know,
that sounds better than Sam and Abida's voices.
It sounds like hell personified in a vocal chord.
It's literally hell, and I will never listen
to those voices again.
If I'm hearing demons get checked out, maybe?
Yeah, I think that is.
I think I'm gonna go get checked out.
Why don't you go to beat his chat and say that as soon as next time you're gonna be banned permanently?
Okay
You're not funny not cute
You're depressing
I'm not hearing demons. I'm hearing beta and salmon's voices and they're literally the voices of demons
Do you think not I
And who's that? What's that? Who's that face is that?
Whose face is that? Is that Bita?
That's Bita's picture.
Things I've done and said. Hmm. You ever hear
sometimes all you need is a little push and you're banned forever by Bita. Bye, bitch.
Alice McQueen? No, I don't like you to do that. You're time out. You're time out. Think of this.
Am I? You don't, you didn't wait for the follow-up. I said it might be an inner ear issue.
Okay, so it was a joke. I didn't, I just timed you out for a minute, okay?
Okay, I need to, maybe I just do my ears checked. I'm sure once I get my ears cleared, their voices will sound beautiful.
I'm talking about these literal voices of hell.
I'm talking about literal, if you just took nails on a chalkboard and then put them in
a voice, this is what those voices would sound like.
I don't think it can be any clearer.
Can someone come up here please and talk to me?
I don't think I'm getting through tonight.
I just, I'm not getting the joke.
I'm not, I'm not in like the best mood because you know, I'm worried about my cat and stuff.
I can't see it. I can't see it and I'm sorry. Oh, I'm so sorry
That didn't like like that picture to me
All I can see is a tiny little picture I saw so I just saw a frizzy black hair. I
Don't know say oh my god and not and say it's safe trying to come up
That that's really guys really
That's who's gonna come up sick
I'm gonna take a deep breath
Really no one's to see yeah exactly no one's to see the baby pickle
They've been following the Artemis too. Yeah, I can fly in the sky
and I'm falling around a space shuttle.
That's not even probably real.
That's what I'm doing.
Check into Mental Health Institute.
I need to have, I'm pushing 50.
Who talks like that?
Who said that?
Christine said that, I think.
She said, I'm closer to 50 than I am.
Yeah, I'm 45.
I mean, yeah, if you, yeah, you can say five to like 50.
But it's like it was to say Christine's age. She's closer than 90 than she is to 50
She's closer to a hundred. Let's let's wrap. Let's do it. Let's do a big roundup
Thank you, thank you, thank you. I'm here every night guys. I'm here every night
Good Lord
What the frickin frack some of these people
Greasy hair is called getting right out of the shower. You understand the difference in wet hair and greasy hair
Here's really greasy. I just shampooed it
You see
I'm a greasy here. Okay
You have a greasy
Spirit and you should go to get that checked out. I think you need to go to an oil change
Band
Wow, just you're just making it easy for me some of you people
Yeah, good people here, but wow
Yeah, I think they have a greasy spirit. They're greasy than the fun. Oh
Olivia Newton-John, I love it. I have a song for you Olivia. It's from this movie Xanadu Olivia. I'm gonna sing it. It's called magic
He goes like this
it goes come take my hand you should know me i've always been in your mind you know i will be kind
i'll be guiding you building your dream has to start now there's no other road to take
You won't make a mistake, I'll be guiding you
You have to believe we are magic
Nothing can stand in our way
Don't let your aim ever stray
And now it gets high
And if all your hope is gone
I'm sorry
Destiny will arrive
I'll bring all your dreams alive
For you
From where I stand
You are home free
The planets align
So rare
There's promise in the air
I'm sorry I lost my voice
And I'm guiding you
through every turn I'll be near you I'll come anytime you call I'll catch you
when you fall I'll be guiding you you have to believe we are magic nothing can
stand in our way you have to believe we are magic don't let your aim ever
I'll bring all your dreams to life for you. I'll bring all your dreams to life for you.
Thank you. Thank you. I'm here. I know it's too high. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I lost my voice
during the Christine voice. I made a mistake. That's my karma. I tried to make a funny Christine voice
I didn't try my best I'd love to talk to Lala like Lala the only person that's
trying to come up with a SIG I feel like I'm maybe literally in hell unless
something like an angel comes on the panel I'd rather talk to an angel
had enough talking to demons and hearing these demon voices coming out of these
channels I should never have gone to like Sam man to beat us
No, don't go. No, don't go. He's I'll ban him. I'll ban him. He's not here. He won't bother you. I promise you
I won't let him on panel. I won't let him in the chat
Is she a drunk I'm not gonna put a jacket on her. She's a bitch
Not a drunk. I don't know if she's a drunk. She says she's not
Where's the top mod? I don't know McQueen. I need you. I need my I need my bro, bro
I need my my quackers. Is there a quacker in the house?
Sigg left he left he's onto his rumble bullshit with zero viewers. Hey Chanel. How are you?
Have I have literal frog in my throat from Chris from imitating Christie
Hi
And that you know, you know what phi means it means
But it's like psyche. It's like the mind and it's like a pitchfork
It's like a three friend thing. It's like it's a you
Yeah, oh and Lala left because you heard stig was around
Unless I was just trying to come up panel I didn't say he's gonna bother anybody or be on the panel
It's okay
I need to shut my door before the police are involved.
And tonight, I cannot deal with that.
I hear my neighbors like listening outside.
I'm just gonna close the windows.
Hold on.
Trig!
The thing is with cats, they usually don't go too far.
But if they kind of get lost, they kind of,
you can't spell the name.
Oh yeah, the police have been here like at least like.
10 times in the last like month a
Literal frog. Yeah, and its name is Christine
You want to see it
All right, I'm just kidding. Okay, I'm sorry. I was just kidding. I don't think it's a literal frog, but
Isn't it? Well, they're just down the street and it's like and the guy came come it's like either well, not too
I mean, they're really cute. I
Think police are pretty I love the blue pants with the
nice tight butt and stuff
the handcuffs
Little star
that hats
They're like that serious face. I love I do like police
Have a I have a police fetish. I have a fetish. I'm the prisoner and I'm being strip searched and cavity checked. Oh
Yeah, I'm not wearing blue pants tonight, but it's kind of like it's kind of similar to this
Well, I'm a bold chair and like that
I am so sorry, I am so sorry.
You thought it was a pet frog? I don't have a pet frog.
I dissected it and inserted it in my throat.
It lives there now.
You saw the outline?
Well, I have it. Yeah, I know I wasn't kidding. Hey, you know, have you ever seen me in my speedo?
You know my speedo has a big like this huge piece of foam I put in the front of it a
Cheek a little bit. I'm a grower not a shower
And sig is a grower not a show or not a grower no
Egg plant yeah, I have an egg plant a literal egg plant
You know what's really good? Take an eggplant, you slice it up a little bit, but not like
all the way. And then you pour olive oil on it. If you have a piece of garlic in there,
wrap it in foil, throw it in the oven, 45 minutes, 350. You're going to like vegetables
again. You know, I used to think brussel sprouts were gross, just because it would just be
plain brussel sprouts. And now I even think they taste good. But if you should taste my
Thanksgiving Brussels sprouts. Oh
My god, it's like X. It's like they're the best
They're so good
Things that you think are bad could be actually listen like thing that is gone Lauren left. I mean
Look, there's just 20 people in here. That's okay
Cooking stream. I'm gonna make a John Wayne casserole. Okay. I need to clean my kitchen really good
And then I'll do a John Wayne casserole. It's here's I'll tell you how I make it
You get a casserole dish, and you get some Pillsbury Grand's biscuits, and you like
push the biscuits down on the casserole dish, okay?
And then you bake that for like 20 minutes.
Take them out, so you have a nice like half-baked bottom for us.
You put on like a few pounds of taco meat on it.
You put on bell peppers, you know, you take bell peppers and onions and stuff to slice
them up.
Put those on it tomatoes, and then you take you mix cheese sour cream and mayonnaise and
Then you put that on top, and then you put jalapenos on it. I
Know I'm gonna check my discord. I know it here. Do you hear that? Yeah, it's going nuts
To me to what's going on over there
I don't know why it is cuz I look and there's like not messages. There's like no new messages
I don't know what's wise make it so much noise
Is it my
Is it in my server? Hold on.
I don't know where it's coming from. I'm just gonna turn it off.
I don't see, like, it's not...
What the fuck?
I don't know. I don't know where it's coming from.
I don't see, it's not the private messages.
Now I don't know what it's from. I'm just gonna I'm just gonna exit it
It's kind of annoying. Someone wants my attention somehow
Let's go to the kitchen and cook
I'd love to I don't have any ingredients right now. I do have like a
bacon cheeseburger and some fries to put in my air fryer
But I need to read I'm gonna put the fries on my in the air fryer
And I'm gonna put the burger in and then I have some food right now
But I don't want to get too drunk too quick because it's a fun night
That's what I call cooking
Never cookin
Yeah, maybe
Here I want to hold I want to pick a pretty flower. Hold on. Oh, it's okay. I'll hold the flower for a little bit. I
Got these cool beautiful flowers
Gorgeous
Oh, oh, oh now it's perfect
Look how beautiful those are the love yellow roses. I
Swear these are my cup like favorite color flower. They are
Can I fuck you
I think I need music, that's fine. Hold on, just give me a second.
Friendship.
Oh my gosh, sorry, the pedal's gone.
Perfect, I think that's perfect
Smoking tobacco by the way
Here's what you do you just pour the petals
I feel like I'm in prom you know I here's how popular was high school
I didn't get nominated for I think I was nominated for prom king but
there's this couple and so they were prom king queen so but I ended up being the prom prince
my senior year with another girl in my class we're kind of like a little bit of the
Not outcast, but we were a little bit of the
Odd odd ones we're just a little bit of the odd ones out a little bit but I ended up getting
Boated for one part out of second place
It's one of the yellow roses
For my bouquet I got
The prom prince. I don't know they just as a special category. I guess it created us for me. So I wouldn't feel
Because the prom key and queen were kind of obvious. They were kind of like a shoe in
But my school, you know, we had a small school and so they're like, okay, so I was the prince of the prom
Quack quack. Yeah
I was the prince
Hey, we have a guest let's welcome
From the beautiful state of New York
He keeps the cocaine cartels in business
Pull it over pull it over. Oh
What do you know? You're getting you're getting hit by the quacks my man. This is a quack attack
The quack five
Let's say he's the quack five by the way. He's the fifth quack
And the five, you know what number five is that's like a V and that means
Big victory for us, you know
Let me see. I do have like a little I have to you know, I'm a little bit slow with these sound effects, but
Let me try this one. Let me see. I have a sound. I have a sound effects that I want to play
And play it. Okay. I got it ready guys. You want to hear the sound effect? It's not a dolphin. Hit it
Okay, okay, I got it page pagey pagey pagey no page is not here yet, but I have a sound for
None of your shit
Like what it did?
Quack-quack cycling
You're running
Discussion they're technical. Well, that's cool. You see you made red. I read it. Yeah
Yeah, that's cool. Oh, I just I just started. Oh, yes, I guess who's here
Right come on pull up come on come on
Checking on boy
Should we talk from the quack attacks as Maya cloud tax as dolphin
Quackers
Quacker with his Rubik's Cube. Let's thank you. Look at that Rubik's Cube. That's the new Rubik's Cube
You gotta follow the center so you got the orange put together you got half the yellow
Yeah, that would jar me insane. I could barely do the regular Rubik's Cube. Honestly, I will get one side of the green or the yellow
I'm on this side the opposite side
Disaster and I already got a bit wrong. It could do the Rubik's Cube. I'm in like a second
with the pink
Next
If you go on YouTube there's little like Chinese kids do that shit in one's minute like
It's nuts that's such a good thing for the brain bro. I hear some sound by the ocean I hear is I hear an ocean sound
Is this is a skill is it a is it a the waves is it something it's just
I hear down by the sea
Yeah, what's that one?
Yeah
On a blanket with my pain
Is where see what it is good. He remembers the shit. I don't even remember it
for
We'll be havin' some fun under the boardwalk, under the sun, under the boardwalk.
We'll be havin' fun under the boardwalk with his fuckin' Speedos, kickin' him in.
Hey!
Oh my god.
To see him bending over but he was twerking the speed was he's gotta be he's got a big
McQueen has your great friend black north that you rock was cool just like canada cry
Happy motherfuckers ain't smart enough to stop night in half the first layer page page
I hear my paging.
I can't whistle anymore because it demeans her.
Paging!
Always calling her stupid exactly that's how she gets home
But she gets lost she has like you know something's wrong with her
She goes our swims, but then we got to put out the call to get her back home
And then she like she she like hits the house blindly like she can't even find the way in so we got to keep doing
And we ready your shit motherfucker
We did we did that was my fault by the way if you're pissed at us
We he pulled out the fucking gang gang
What did Alex say quackalors psyching live we out a team
Quack and me quackering need a quackering need quackering need no quack left behind rule number one right no quack
Guess what behind?
If we had a port mission, we got to go back from you understand
Fuck that. Yup. Yup. You know how much the lead duck always like make sure every duck comes up
The trial that they did hopped over something went up the waterfall or whatever the fuck they wait
no matter what
No duck left
That's like
I don't want to be copyrighted, but I have to show you something that's so perfect right now. Yeah
You're gonna love this
I heard they told you
Is there a duck tattoo on your butt?
No
They said put a duck tattoo on your chest with my my government name. Don't listen to them, please
He's got a flower on his chest look at that yellow box of me. You heard them, right? You heard them dox me, right?
They told you I'm just a quacker Tracy once in on the quack club. Look at that
guys. You want to be a you're
a quacker. She's a quacker.
Guys, I have something to show
you. I might have to end this.
I don't want to be copyrighted
but this is let's say huge
picture. Let me show it. Let
him show it bro. He's trying
to show something. What is it?
Okay. You got it ready? It's
real quick here. Here we go.
Show me your quack. Show me
your quack is the most
screenshot. I'm a screenshot
of your quack. Oh.
Oh, we out the kiddie leading the cat. Yeah, who did that? What's that? What?
Look at that
Kiddie game
That's
Leaning cats
He's so funny this guy found videos of dogs and cats cuz he's got it all the kiddies in there. You understand
Yeah, he's idea. I respect it. I respect it. That's so
Which one is it is it duck leading cats or just the cats having to take care of the ducklings in school
You put him like an incubator
I don't know what you mean by it, but I don't know that you got to break it down to me
Okay, no, it's like not because I love cats and I love ducks and stuff. It's not anything about it dude
I have my own cat. Yeah, I really do like ducks. I really do like ducks like y'all don't understand
That's why I chose I read like I was like, you know what?
I'm gonna be just trying to incorporate the quack gang with some with some kitty
I personally like ducks as an animal like mom cat is also mother duck duck things are very clingy to mom
Okay
Well, that's a real because that's insane of the real
This is so so fucking cool
She's just so fucking cool. I've never heard like you say that
Okay, here we go, let's go
You see it? Okay, I'm gonna here it is right here. Here we go
Here you go. One two three. Are you ready?
Why does that remind me of Arthur right off the bat with his dog feet?
the ground
That's us following Stikey, that's us following Stikey, that's us following Stikey, that's
us following Stikey, that's us following Stikey, that's us following Stikey, that's us following
Stikey, that's us following Stikey, that's us following Stikey, that's us following Stikey,
that's us following Stikey, that's us following Stikey, that's us following Stikey, that's us
What do you think you got to read me through the lines of Ronys? Who do you think the cat is in this picture?
So basically Ronys is protecting us because we're just little dogs if anything, you know that kind of go crazy
Katniss Everdeen! I love it!
Look at the Quackers. I'm the one in the front. I'm the first quack. I'm the one in the back, bro.
That's why you're the one that was corruption corruptions. Oh, he's the one by the center. He's like, yeah, no, no, but that's Roni's
That's Roni's we're following the little kitty. I love it
The way he's leaving the way cuz we're lost dogs
We think we're you know, but without Roni's we'd be lost
Yep
Right wrong wrong. Yeah, and he waited for his love. He could have dipped
Yeah, bro, we're not rolling rolling rolling
Rollin, AK-8 Rooney, Rooney's AK-8 Rooney, he's gonna dip just now
And look at Rooney's
Like, come on, quack, give me a little quack
Look at Rooney Rooney, the Rooney Rooney
And we're just like quack quack
They're like, look at us protect them, we just surround them
Yeah, you saw that? How you surround them?
You saw that?
Like, bodyguards, Alex
Like, party guards.
With little Quaker guards, Quaker guards.
Oh my god, the heifer, we, we found summer?
Where's this bitch been?
Baby, I've been looking for you!
You are so one!
Did we just...
Was that a happy one?
I think Christine was manipulating Summers.
And if not...
If Summers was getting manipulated by Christina,
she feels that that's right.
I think she was getting manipulated by her.
I think... I think Christine was...
I think Psyche's trying to bring us back to the Heifers.
You understand?
Like, stop the beef, guys.
And we're just fighting his ears like
Dicks like no mods for none of you and so's only you
Summers
He took everyone's mind
You know, he's leading us to the havers
Look, oh my god
Hi Christine!
This is the funny shit I've seen
Oh shit
Oh my god
That's something
Hello
I'll move up against some shit
Alex
We're out of here
Hey yo Corruption
Are you ready Corruption?
We're out of here
we could care less we're just flapping in the mud like we just quacking out we
quacking out just quacking up Roni's taking his little chill time by
myself like to write the quacks are good I'm gonna go over here do my Rony thing
get some McDonald's get a couple of blunts a couple of cookies
And then we're just so round.
Roni, Roni, make me mad, quack, quack.
Yo, look at Alex, look at Alex, the main one.
Talk about, um, I'm the one chilling.
Like, I got my design now.
The main one, the main one is up with Alex right there.
He's like, um, thank you, come back.
like that
look at you guys trying to be good
for a little ranchie
that's all it does to quack squad
that's the funniest shit I've ever seen
they come dying
yo psyche use the hilarious mother fuck
I swear to god
you like that
oh my god let's talk about it
yo that shit was hilarious psyche
for real for real
yeah
that was the whole thing
I know where you made it or found it either. Oh, you like this is not bro. That's mushroom shit
I need mushrooms for that. We got to take shrooms and watch that again
Yeah, I'm gonna be fucked up. Yo, it's like he they told you put my real name on your body for real
No, I'm you know, I said today I said that mr. Extendo I went to his channel
I said hey, did you see you're gonna do two new tattoo to joke or mr. Extendo
And he said you had a two-touch to you and I said yeah.
No, on Stephen King's page, on Stephen King's page.
Stephen King's page.
And Chris Cavs told you to put my name on your body.
Wow.
I'm going to do it on the other side.
but I don't joke her
Don't do that. Don't do that. He'll put my he said my god. He knocks me at the top
I mean, he's not gonna do that, bro. He doesn't listen to idiots Ronis. He's not dumb
Big haters big hate of us. He hates the quack squad. He don't even like you psychics
I don't know Joker. Yeah, that was the best video ever, man. Jesus
Don't joke right now tattoo. Is it we got tattoo and you get what you get is that I got property of mr.
Extender on a red butt cheek
And he's like, I'm not gonna just get out I have buck BKG
of the
But I got you know, yeah
Yeah, put my snap of my sake enough for months
You gotta be part of the quack squad out there come on quack out there you gotta be just like me
Yeah, they're funny he was laughing at it actually
I know he liked it. I know he liked it. He said it's Mufflap fell off his truck
And now there was like you know a company you work for that your Mufflaps are falling off and Arthur was laughing
You know, they're cool kids bro. They're cool guys. They're funny
I thought Arthur was a dick, but you know, I'm starting to pee too. I used to pick out there was the biggest dick
But he's actually cool
Or to Arthur too
Yeah
They're cool. You know Arthur's really cool. I had him I had him on this morning with like it was Arthur and that was RG
I was watching I was lurking you saw me once I write and then I say I just watch
RG was pressing Arthur a little bit and like and then Arthur took this whole story about how he used to be a wrestler
Do you know Arthur used to be a wrestler and got kicked out of
Show the pedo at all. I would at all. And I don't know
Why he was kicked out, but it's like I was like I want to find his channel and it's like he said his name was
SC Steve or something like that. He was from South Carolina. I said, what did you wear when you wrestled?
He said if you were a speedo and stuff
I looked for it, but I couldn't find it if anyone can find Arthur. I'm a wrestling video
Rock the link
Simple. Yeah
Yeah, just drop the link for Arthur's video like I want to see Arthur like I
Literally kind of do you have a crush on Arthur?
No, listen, we'll try it. It's like he's trying to say is tomorrow is not fast enough. Please drop it now
I was asking the guy like knew the guy knew everything else about Arthur's life, but he didn't have the link to like the
you know
Arthur's
Yeah, oh my god. Yeah, but then today I was like he was I asked him again
I was like he kept he kept like denying me. He kept like just doing his own voice
I was like Arthur do sweepy inside
Yo, bro, you're friends with Alexander Mayer's again. How amazing is that?
How do you see that coming?
So that's why I'm never gonna talk again because I told them I'm a
And no it has not
the
Yeah, I'll shut up right, but I'm not trying to like you know be over be aware. That's all I gotta say is be aware, brother
She was impressed
Genuine I'm just say that hope is genuine
Yeah, she's not stupid man, I was wrong. I thought be there was the one that could be saved. It's the opposite
I think that ship and sail
I think you're getting one relationship and one out of the two is not bad man
Alex, take Christine out of the picture and I bet you...
But definitely all the times your man is the better one for him at the end of the day
Take Christine out of the picture and talk about this guy
Man is the worst one
Real repair
Just take Christine out of the picture
She's the problem
I don't know about that that one. I think that it's like I had my chance with the with the beta. I tried
For a long time and it's like she didn't have an understanding of like me basically. She doesn't she doesn't get me, but
I'll say that Alexander Alexander did this dear John video and it's like I saw it
I didn't know about IRL news. That's why I didn't see it
I was looking at IP to wiki and I'm like, what's this guy talking about?
They talked and made up and then I found it today. I'm like, holy shit. They did
You guys had like a one like an hour conversation. Yeah apologizing a little bickering back and forth, but awesome
Yeah, I mean it was like it was good and it's like I just as long as it's pieces of and uh, yeah
That's easy. You just wanted to acknowledge that she didn't say for you to off yourself and you were like I don't want an apology
It's all good and
I do what you your friends with her again, so you want that relationship back
How amazing is that because that meant a lot to you brother. It's like not like and her
Friendship is a gift, you know friendship is another she took me by surprise as well because I didn't think she would do that
Like I thought she was just a bitch like you know unforgiving bitch, but she's not she has a heart
It's like we're just going back and forth like I swear. We're both the same birthday. We have the same birthday
It's like as much as our little you can believe in astrology. I think that there's like
Kind of understanding make her out the picture and everything's going to be fine
Yeah, I promise everybody that
Christine
Admitted that she comes up here to throw when I'm talking about cooking bother by the way. We're totally my accent your mayor's
But cool, but you know, yeah, fuck Christine when I told my Christine she didn't make up with Psyche
I'm done. No fool me once shame on you fool me twice shame on me
Yeah, Sharon was here is awesome. Well, you know yesterday or she yesterday she was in my chat
I missed the message, but she said she said psyche wake up. It's Easter
You know get up and she's like you have a good panel going. She's like talk to Alexander McQueen. He's an expert in fashion
you know
Oh, that's what she said too. I didn't know that she was like it's funny
She's like sometimes I think she was being funny to she's like sometimes I think
That the psychic show should be called the McQueen show and I was like that's funny
And then she was like it's funny how
Whoever Alexander McQueen is is using that name because that McQueen
Fashion designer was really really really into that Lilith
character or person or spirit. I had no clue about that.
She called you a demon. How crazy is that?
You didn't know about that? I had no clue about that.
So Alex accidentally intertwined with the demon.
No, I picked up my name. I sent him a queen for a reason when I did it,
but it had nothing to do with him.
I accidentally intertwined with the demon side.
But the factors is like that, and I was all like connecting now.
McQueen had a deep connection with this littlest thing that psyche like
Well
Who is Lilith and why didn't I send him a queen care about Lilith I thought that's come straight you made up psyche
I swear to God. I thought I was like
Listen, that's the devil's right hand put it like that simple. It's okay. I'm talking to psyche brother. Can you let the guy answer?
And what is my queen care about
It says in the Bible it says in the beginning God created man and woman and then later
Look a few verses later
it says and then like God created e from Adam's rib and so in like the
Torah or the Talmud like the rabbi has expanded on it said, okay, well, there's actually he there's a first woman
Name Lilith and yeah, and you can look it up
And it's like and then she actually knew the name God because Adam wanted to be on top and then Lilith said no
I don't want to be dominated
I want to be on top and so she didn't even want to be on top she wanted equality but Adam was this to see on dominance
She says I'm fucked this. This is not a character. You made up with a I this is actually like a thing this littlest person
And then I turned the Queen
Adores it or worships that person as I said just said
And did you know Alexander McQueen was also like a pedo or something he was like deep
I had a pair of Alexander McQueen shoes at one point my friend got to me. Yeah, he was like on some Epstein shit supposedly
I don't know about that stuff, but I know
Madison Avenue
Yeah, there's a store of Alexander McQueen store, but Lilith was like
He's a high-end designer for rich people, bro. What a pair of sneakers cost $2,000
You know
Who's Lilith right?
Yeah, that's my point. I have no idea who Lilith is. That's what I'm trying to get at
Like Lilith actually like so she like said that she was able to say the name of God
Yeah, but that's not in the Bible. What do you learn about her?
It doesn't say like Lilith because because because there's a Jewish oral tradition called the Talmud
And it was an oral tradition and so the rabbis would expand upon biblical things by because there's the name in the Bible
It's actually a word in the Bible. That's called it means screech out in the Bible
But yeah, the original McRib. That was Eve.
Is he evil though?
Well, the devil's right hand man, the right hand lady.
Yeah, okay. Here's the thing. Okay.
So it's like the devil's wife or like the devil's assistant?
Like the souls of the basically...
That unborn that didn't survive or something like that like she was that those were her children and stuff like that
It wasn't like she killed them, but she's like she was given and so that there's like but also like gauging
Beemons, right psyche supposedly well, like they well they would say that but it's like she was actually like
Because that's what you we call incidents, bro
I think she was like there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was a there was
Well, it does different thank you. Can you give us the explanation on a video for he can understand?
Explain it to this man is hard
I've been a video called the truth about lily's but outside but I have something about uh, and I can play it
Um, here's something called, you know, I have the, okay, I'll just, I'll just do this.
The music is a little bit...
That's the easiest way, because explaining it to Alex is a little difficult, so just
play it.
Okay, yeah, I'll explain.
I'll explain.
Here we go.
So this is, um...
This is the this is the story here. We all share this page. Okay, but and this is like it
I hope you can like comment on it and stuff, but this is the story but it's like a fairy tale, right?
It's just another fictional character
Like, you know, and you can say the Bible
How we can explain it
Yeah, I here's here's I made a video and here's the video I made and this is like called you know
And it's like this is like time to idea do people worship this thing
You know in like sacrilege shake hands on the bay on the bathroom that thing you put it. Do you see it on the screen?
Okay, there you go. You're watching this here you go
Not the cartoon version, not the cheap, poor movie version.
Not the lazy, patriarchal bedtime story where any woman who says no gets stamped with horns and thrown into the dark.
Let's talk about the truth.
Because Lilith is one of the most misunderstood female figures in the world.
She has been called demon, devour, seductress.
child killer, destroyer, nightmaster, she has been turned into a-
She is dancing like my ex-wife and every other girl I've ever had.
A threat with a female voice, and that alone should tell you something.
Whenever a culture is afraid of female power, it does not simply disagree with it.
It mythologizes against it, it drags it into the underworld, covers it in ash,
gives it claws, and then says, see.
This is what happens when a woman will not submit, that is Lillith's story, or at least, that is what was done to her.
Now let's be accurate, Lillith does not stroll cleanly out of Genesis with a main tag that says,
Hello, I'm Adam's first woman. That is not how the text feels. The famous story of Lillith.
as the first woman country, especially in Jewish folklore and the alphabet of Ben-Sera, where
she is described as being made from the same earth as Adam, refusing to lie to me. She insists on
equality, accuses subservience and leaves Eden rather than obey. Think about that. She does not
obey. Are you kidding me? She does not. She does not stay. So she was Adam's first wife,
not corruption, not some cosmic crime, the offensives refusal,
Lilith becomes intolerable the moment, she says.
I was made from the same blood.
That line is the lightning strike in me,
because once a woman says she is equal in origin,
equal in spirit, equal in authority over her own body,
the whole machinery of domination starts rattling with loose iron.
The story cannot permit that without consequence. So the rebel becomes the monster. This is how demonization works.
I'm psyched. I think that's enough for me to talk about.
Older than Twitter, older than tabloids, older than gossip circles with fake holos and knives behind their backs.
First, they fear the woman, then they rename the fear as Hibiru, then they pretend they
are protecting the world from her.
Lilith is the ancient blueprint for that trick.
Her roots likely reach deeper than medieval folklore.
Scholars connect her name and traits to older Mesopotamian renaissance traditions, to
Lyle and Lilith's figures associated with night, danger, and experience.
There is also a debated biblical appearance in Isaiah 34-14, where the Hibirutom Lilith
appears in a desolate wilderness scene, though translators and scholars differ on exactly how
to render it. In rabbinic and megafolk traditions, Lilith becomes a knight being feared especially
around child-breaking infants, which is why amulets and bokeh angelic names were used to ward her
off. So no, the truth is not that Lilith was originally handed to us as a mute feminist heroine
The truth is more interesting than that.
She was feared first.
She was shaped by male anxiety, communal fear, sexual panic,
childbirth, terror, wilderness dread,
and the ancient human habit of giving a face to the dark.
Then something remarkable happened.
She survived the scenario.
Across centuries, Lilith refused to stay trapped inside the world of Saitama.
She kept changing.
She moved through folklore, through mysticism,
through the Talmud, through Kabbalah, through medieval nightmare,
through whispered warnings over Kratos and Horshal.
And in the modern world, women look at this figure,
this conglomerate woman, this exile woman,
this woman-shaped fear object.
and said, wait a sec, maybe the story is upside down.
Maybe the monster is just the woman who would not kneel.
That is the great reversal,
modern Jewish feminist writers, artists,
and thinkers reclaimed literally as a symbol of freedom,
sexual autonomy, spiritual independence,
and rebellion against domination.
Judith Buskoe as famous retelling helped turn from a patriarchal cautionary tale into a figure of female
Even the feminist magazine Lilith founded in 1976 shows how fully that old demon name was
transformed into a banner rather than a coat and that reclaiming matters because myth is never just
Akki Lilith asks a question that still makes people uncomfortable.
What do you call a woman who refuses the role written for her?
If she stays quiet, they call her good.
If she suffers beautifully, they call her ver-
If she nurtures everyone while starving herself, they call her holy.
But if she leaves, if she speaks, if she desires, if she s-
If she names the arrangement as unjust, suddenly the language changes.
Now she's dangerous.
Now she is dark. Now she is unnatural. Now she is too much.
Lilith lives in that accusation. That is why people still respond to her so strongly.
She touches the live wire between female freedom and social punishment.
But, let's go deeper. Lilith is not just rebellion for the sake of rebellion.
She is not chaos as an aesthetic. She is not nearly rage and lipstick.
The core of her power is sovereignty. Sovereignty over the body. Sovereignty over desire.
Sovereignty over speech. Sovereignty over whether she stays in a structure that diminishes her.
That is what makes her fight in the two systems built on her beliefs.
A woman who can be tempted is manageable.
A woman who can be shamed is manageable.
A woman who still wants approval is manageable.
But a woman who no longer accepts false authority, that woman becomes mythic.
And men who cannot control that energy have always had two options, understand it or demonize it.
History shows which option many of them chose now was Lilith, really a goddess, in the strict
She is more often a demonized female figure, a night being, a dangerous spirit, not a goddess in the formal devotional sense.
But in modern spiritual and symbolic language, many people experience her as a dark goddess untold,
because she has come to represent rejected feminine powers, forbidden knowledge, erotic autonomy, and sacred refusing.
That is not ancient consensus. That is modern reinterpretation.
but it is a meaningful one and honestly that distinction is important because truth does not
need fake certainty and it does not become as powerful because the story evolved over time.
She becomes more powerful. It shows that a story can be wrestled with, a demon can be reexamined.
A curse can be turned into a blessing, a warning can be turned into a map, limit is the patron
saint of difficult women and I mean that as a compliment.
She is the patron saint of women who are called too much, too loud, too angry, too sexual,
too independent, too unwilling to make themselves small.
She is the patron saint of the woman who leads the garden to find herself in the wilderness.
and discovers that the wilderness is where she was meant to be all along.
That is...
Lillith.
Not a cartoon villain.
Not a One Note Goddess sticker.
Not a neat little morality tale.
She is the Echo of Rebellion in a world that rewards confines.
She is the shadow cast by equality when hierarchy cannot bear the one.
She is the name given to the woman who chose herself and was punished for it.
There we go. Sorry the music was a little bit loud in that but yeah, she actually has good Maya's right
Yeah
Great. Yeah, I was listening to I was listening but I'll say in the rebitcher
I'll try to show you. I was a little bit loud. It's better. It's maybe just around the volume. It's intense man
That was a crash course
Yeah
Go
She's part of my
My question to this is like
Distributive was one of the first right maybe before Eve, right?
Yeah, right. Yeah, let's say what if
Let's say yeah, but that wasn't in the Bible in the Bible it starts I don't mean
We start speaking Alex, I just want to drop it quick is in the back. What if Lilith was the one that ate the apple and got sent to the devil?
Lucifer because she violated and then out comes the second rib
There's also good night corruption
Good night in the back chat. Yeah, thank you. Good night. Good night, dude. It's actually said in the Bible
Man and woman were created
Equal equal out of the and I think she was made from the desert sand and Adam was made from the mud or something
Like or clay Adam means red, you know, that means red
It means like the red red and that and that yeah, there he was made from the earth, right?
Yeah, I'm in his room for the clay and the guy probably wait. No, maybe
Presentation of Eve eating the apple because she didn't submit her pictures of Lilith. Yeah
All right, no, that's the evil version of we
There's the one that didn't listen to God and ate the apple and defied
She probably got sent to Lucifer like you wanted to find me like him well go with him
No, she's one of her little princesses, no, she's like a princess of, of hell.
Yeah, you're, okay, you can't hear something too.
Think about it, Alex, if she was the first, if she was the first, if she ate the apple,
she'd abide God's word, just like Lucifer did.
You think he wouldn't set her down there as instinct?
No, I think Eve is Lilith wants to eve bit into the apple
There's an interesting representation I can show you real quick
This is just a picture and there's a there's several pictures, but I can show you this one
This is kind of like a representation
And it says oh IP dot to be in a pedestal, okay, and this is like a representation perhaps that we can make you think about it
image. Oh, if he does APG. Yeah.
This was before Eve. Yeah.
This is what I'm saying. She
could have been the possibility
that she could be the third
There you go. There you go.
What's up ghosts? Yeah, I had a question for you. You don't mind
Well, I mean yeah, well if you go into goddesses and stuff, but also it's like there's representations of her as the serpent in Eden
Right. Are you saying that Eve survived that long and she became Lilith and what are you saying?
I don't know. Lilith was before Eve. She was the first woman and then Eve was created out of the rib
which is like kind of subservient to man to be like the kind of like
The
Not like she wanted to be on
Picture look at the picture. There's a woman on the floor
Right look at that. I thought I thought that was the roots for a second Alex, but then I had to take a
After she transformed into Lilith once she bit that fucking apple
Well
Evil twin version of all of us the devil inside
Victim and then Eve was like because because if you go to that what the serpent said to said to Eve he
He whispered something to her. He was like a whisper
menstrel or been ms. What about
what about
Adam got a vengeance for loose
women will be service forever
because God sent his bitch to
Lucifer. Now that's his hope
she's stuck up for women
like I'm not listening to you
loser. I'm not kneeling to you
I'm biting. I want to know the truth
you want to be equal command
for servient and because
Adam insisted on being on top
So then
All this is hypothetically speaking
Ideas and stuff to talk about and think about is not necessarily this is exactly what happened in real
Exactly we have no clue
Yeah, we weren't there, no one was there, but it's like
Exactly
I pretend to be speaking
Bro, what we know is Nintendo and fucking subways, you know, and fucking birthday
Bro, I know what I see, I don't believe it, but if I can't see it, I don't believe it
that's got to be a way to figure it out and like that seems to you see love can you see kindness can you see I mean it's like
You want me to bend you over? Oh, that's Alex job. Oh my gosh
Well, I have one more. I have one more. I made like one of my first music videos was called Bob. Let me lose
Alex how many how many I drink Alex Alex you have my count
Yeah, what's this? What's this real quick? I'm gonna put on this real quick. I think you'll guys will like
Bitch, I did my first videos that I made guys never
Hey, you know, I'm not right or not wrong. It's like these are ideas and it's like it's fun to think about
But who knows what's right or wrong? It's like, you know, but um
We got it. Hold on
But someone's right and someone's wrong. Isn't that scary?
Even with the
I
Mean this video is my first video is about because I have a Lilith in Scorpio, so
She rises in shadows, fears and sorrows.
May I permission?
Lilith in Scorpio, my anima, flame.
Whispers my secrets, calls out my name.
Dude that beat drop was heavy
Yeah, wait
Abel and Kane the fourth person on earth and then murders are started
That's crazy
ZENMAN!
She's not real following
What do you think people just popped out of thin air there was a time when there was four people on earth
Thing that is bullshit. Well, what I mean, it's like
Well, I don't know
I don't mean to keep leaving my Wi-Fi is acting up. That's my bad
Don't hit the link. I want to hear your fucking philosophy on this
Conversation
What ten people just popped up?
Alex I got this thing
Station Alex wall out you ain't know how psyche is he's drinking on brother come and have a conversation
I got Modelo hello
You ask me what I'm drinking on Modelo hello. I'm on number eight bitch
Wow
After he hits nine numbers
I'm responsible for MF for the first date once he hits nine
My dick goes
Exactly the womb. Once you come out of the womb, the light is torture.
Life is torture, buddy. We come from the darkness. That's womb.
The light is hell. That's what we see in creative bullshit.
Alex, the meaning of born is you start dying. How crazy is that?
No shit because you you start returning back home now. You're in hell
You're in this fucking hologram life with the light
Dean things shadows creating people. It was bullshit. Well, bro. We come from the darkness. That's home my friend
Remember when you were in the womb nice and nestled completely
You were in complete darkness that was when you were in heaven
Oh
Me goes to psyche hello, dr. Smile. I'm telling you that's where the Bible coincides
The quack squad is out
I don't talk please
That is the same thing the chicken or the egg what came first the chicken or the egg
I would see the chicken came first
Alex Alex, you know I created the chicken
created man
Any and human
That's how it happens a hundred humans getting just got dropped off on a mountain cliff one day and so
Thing that is the moron
Was very like nerdy guy and he said you know what he said the first day of class he said okay first
It verse rule of physics. You were sexy
Okay, he said the first rule of physics is it's all bullshit. That's what he said to me
He said it's all ideas and the human mind of how we explain things
But it's all ideas. It's not anything really provable. It's theories and
You know what I say they say they say a manifest make your ideas into reality
Who blocked my call does somebody kind of like I don't know
you know who blocked them it's only two people only two people got the wrench you guilty
hey alex you're the only one that has a written but that's what my high school teacher my physics
teacher explicit he said this is all bullshit physics is bullshit it's just basically human
ideas to explain things but it's all theories ideas not physics all these little atoms that we can't
Think that it things on a map mod here things on a mod. I think that's a lot to see you're not physics
That is for everything Alex Alex know how I get
I trust my whoever my mod is. If someone blocked you, you probably deserved it. I'll just say that
Talking snake and a guy walking around of the fig leaf overish long and it will write. I mean, it's like but these are stories
These are ideas, you know, these are
It's like lost to see the dog. That's not all the true. No, these are like basically called mythology myth
You know, but it's like do they have to study the mind not physics
Not in my chat, okay
Then why would you do that thing you block mr. Mike Hall
You got beef with him
Thing that is come up a thing. We need
I
Saw us marshals today rescue a kidnap little boy
five years old
US Marshals got wind of where he was
They rolled up three black man's
When in the house found the kid
The poor little kid brother, they brought him out in a blanket, the kidnappers had him in the closet under a blanket
Swat team, three vans of swat, pulled up to this fucking house, rescued the kid
And then they had the kid in the van and he's so cute, he's like, are you taking me to my mommy?
And they're like, we're taking you to your mommy, man, don't worry, are you hungry?
Yeah, I'm hungry, can I have a cheeseburger? He's so funny
And you got it, my little man, we're taking you to your mom right now
They are dogs. How can you hate the woman for a simple?
Did you will rescue little kids?
Like hiding in classes from people that kidnapped them
There's a lot there and
There's people that counter you and you have to love those motherfuckers and back them up
Yeah, I'm gonna put the link up again guys if he wants to join us
Not everyone deserves to be in jail with people like that
Don't forbid your little kid got kidnapped one day, bro. Who's gonna rescue it? Not you
You as Marshalls, baby. I'ma turn it to taking me good. You stupid. I think guys
I think I have a great panel tonight. I think this is like a really great conversation
People blame it for dogs and it is of stupid shit. Imagine how I will get if my if my child you take it
I'm not sure even what the fuck you're talking about am I just dumb or
Think about that twice
She's a dog. You call them dubs
I told you go after his nice motel was not responsible exactly
Say I dox off a basic shit, right?
Imagine if somebody fucking my family takes my family you sir. Oh, Jesus Christ
I'm not gonna lie I didn't listen to what he just said because he's slurring it's he's slurring so hard
Like did you understand what he just said?
Alex translate
Do you want me to translate?
Let's speak real speak dumb dumb guys by the way Alice today. I was they would
Alice today have me delivered that food
And flea medicine for the cats and stuff. And thank you
Thank you, Alex, okay
What you say
I
Don't know
Dumb mother fuck I said if I had people bitching about me doctor
No, he's not back yet, but I have hope they'll he sometimes comes back in the middle of night
I mean, I hope he's getting some pussy. I mean, you know
Hope he's okay
That that delivery I was like fuck this motherfucker. I got cats
Trixie
Trixie's missing brother. Do you guys know about that the little cat Trixie?
He hasn't been home in a day
Lolita, okay, he's fine. It's Trixie. I'm sure he's fine. She's worried a little bit about him
He's probably in Las Vegas. He got caught up with some pussy in Vegas
By tomorrow one day. Oh, no Alex one day I sent him to go get fish tacos, right and his cat was um in the tree
Oh, yeah, Freya, that was Freya. She's like a raccoon, you know
Hey, my other also the other night
I had a cat named Marbles that I had and he came inside and all the cats were like
Oh, they're all like growling and stuff and he's fucking feel like he's like fucking so big
He's like so big and fat and stuff like that and it's like and then he just ran back out and stuff
He like just came in real quick
He like I think I touched him real quick and then he like just ran back out, but um
he stopped by and said hi and so it's like he's big and so he's obviously well fed and stuff
and I've had other cats come by with air tags on them or collars or-
He can't feed them, don't always come back y'all.
Yeah, but I don't have, there's no shelter, there's no animal shelters in the city because
we don't need them because there's no stray cats because all the cats-
Make their way into a home because people will just yeah people take in the cats and stuff like that cats
Sometimes they don't they want to be an only cat ever see the Simpsons were you know their cat was named snowball too or whatever
But she
Okay, dude, thank you for coming
All right, bro charge that shit
There's the third quack
Yeah, well she went in the quack team. We got a quack gang going. Oh, thank you. I'm part of the ghost. You don't want in
No
Well ghost a little brat come on
this is
the
I don't know. Ghost. I'll be so
first thing that is. I want him
up here. If you don't want him
up. Okay. Thing that is. Come
on. Thing that is. You didn't
join because he probably didn't
join because of Alex or maybe
he just doesn't want to join. I
don't know. I don't know if he
didn't join because of Alex. I
don't know. Maybe it's because
of me. Who knows? I think
Nick Johnson went up once in on
this quack quack or love. Oh,
What are you doing right now?
Fair what I'm saying, but yeah
Okay, I forgot I forgot but it's only I'm okay. Well, I'm a stigma but I'm also like, you know
If I'm accepted by some by some by a few friends and it's like and sometimes
You know, and I'm not like going and attacking people and like having just having them attack people and stuff
I'm just like I just put friendship basically
You know, like friendship. It's not about like
West Side Story. Hey, Officer Crumpke, come listen to me.
Can you, uh, can you ask, uh, uh, I'm sorry, I'm upset to you.
Can you tell me that is why he doesn't want to join?
The thing that is, I don't know why he doesn't. He's mad at me, maybe?
I'll put my link in. I don't know if it's pinned.
Post that shit again. Post it in the chat again if you don't mind.
Okay, I'll post it in the link again in the chat.
Anybody that wants to join. Thank you, Sharon.
Appreciate that.
As a group thing is yeah, but also but also it's like what like I said, it's not about like oh
I'm gonna we're gonna gang up on you is I know it thing that is but it's also like the gang like
You're my boy, but I also like do I not defend thing that is I mean
You will defend people you'll fight with people you'll I mean ghosts is like there
Really, but it's about like you know
Sometimes it's like to be alone sometimes it's to be lonely and it's like to not
like to be lonely brother yeah and sometimes I sometimes I feel alone but
now I'm not well when you feel like that this when you feel alone does not make
me feel like shit
Well, no because I'm used to being alone and it's like and I and alone also it's like the tournament tarot card
It's like I can be alone and I can recharge, you know, it's kind of like I don't want to be around
There's a difference between being alone and feeling alone you sure alone I'm down with that
Gains from acceptance with the right people finally, you know, you feel like you have friends finally, you know
Yeah, like yeah, well, I don't have no argument there along the along the road
Alone then what once you feel like you're alone once you feel like you have no friends
like I've been on some panels where it's hate against one and I feel like I'm alone and
Yeah, I feel some type of way about it, but fuck it.
You know what, it also is like, can strengthen you.
It's like a form of strength, too, to like,
Good point.
Like, you know, to be, to be like all these people
at once ganging up on your dog piling and stuff,
and then it's like,
And then when you win, imagine that.
But even when you lose, it's like,
fuck it, it's eight versus one.
Ain't nobody gonna win that.
But when you actually, you win, it's like, oh fuck.
Yeah, thank you. Thank you. Yeah, I think like it. I think it's like people that support exactly Sharon said supporters like having like people
They have your back and stuff like that and like you care about you and they ask you a weird question
Of course, there's no weird questions only weird answers
Yeah, why do you have your hair?
You see I'm wearing a shirt. I have my hair. Okay. Okay. Okay. You see I'm gonna try into like kind of
You know, because it's like people, it's like when I'm like kind of like messy and counts and dirty, it's like, it's like fine, but it's like...
Show that shirt off, you heard it.
Hey, did you see my new tattoo?
I did.
Did it start with F?
Yeah, you saw that?
Yeah, I seen that.
But you can show it, show it.
Okay, let's show it.
Sport isn't conforming to the group.
I know, but it's also like having like, like a family, okay? Like a family.
Matter of fact, take that whole fucking shirt off, fucking cake.
Do it do it. I don't blame you
There you go, now we now we have
I didn't mean to let off the mother I was laughing because you showed me armpit here. I
Can't laugh for her. She won't let me join her next panel dog who?
Well, I don't know which one. I don't know who. Why are you asking me? You smell like an owl. I don't know who.
Who, who, who, who?
Well, do you see my back tattoo? I have a back tattoo. I don't know if you've ever seen it, but here you go.
I don't think I've ever seen that fucking. I've known you for a while. I don't think I've ever seen that. I might have seen it before.
Well, I don't think I ever paid attention as I give it. I just want to give a little heart right there
That's just a little bit. I'm not trying to be funny a little bit fading. You might need to get that shit redone
I know I this is my action. I first tattoo
Yes, you see it. Oh, it's like a okay. I have a new psyche haters club video
I'm gonna premiere for the chat tonight. I made this psyche haters club. This is just for the people that hate me and it's like
Watch the question. Okay, after right after this your watch is broken. That seems fair
Where the fake get low and the views dry up
Gotta hate the one crooked, gotta sermon half-baked
Say I'm praying for you while these screenshots get saved
Fake are concerned and they're boys poison in the cup
Say I hate drama while they wind it up
Got pearls in a death creep
channel about this channel oh Samuel I don't know I don't know I don't know mr. Sam hello sir to you
what's the channel about the channels about love the channel about understanding the channels about
growth the channels about learning stuff okay I'm gonna walk to the store and you know while we're
on the topic of Lilith I do have like you know it is an astrology thing too it's called black moon
was it you no it was the guy what was his name he recommended a really good song i forgot his name
i don't it's not Hebrew hammer but it's somebody else and he said there's a song called scars by
papa roach it's about it is about anal it's about anal and Hebrew hammer
are you down
I mean, you asked for it, Hebrew Hammer.
You said it.
It's the Chamelea, Chameleons?
Okay, hold on one second.
946, okay.
So I will show you about my astrology,
lower on the topic of Lilith and stuff.
Down to DTF, yes.
Are you?
Hey, Hebrew Hammer.
Yes, I am.
am are you oh oh now don't say Lulu you better not say Lulu or you're done you
say Lou next up okay up guys I think my I think tonight might be my lucky night
Oh, okay. I'm going to take a walk to the store. I do. I do want to thank you. Someone bought a clap token. Someone, um,
someone
donated and further stuff too. Hold on one second.
Um, but you want to hear about like, you know, I can go over your Lilith and astrology too. You're interested
but, um,
I do have like a little video about Lilith and Scorpio like the act. It's not a it's not a music video. It's just about the explanation of it
Okay, one second, and I'm gonna walk to the store, and I'm gonna try to turn on my phone
while I'm walking, but I'm gonna let you the video play first a little bit.
Okay.
I'm sorry I'm blushing I'm sorry I'm blushing I'm sorry I'm sorry okay I gotta go for a walk
before I forget it but hold on a second and you have like this is about my astrology so
um and I'm gonna put it on it's not the music is much better in this one
this maybe it'll explain some things about me that you maybe didn't know because this is very
About my sign horn, I love it. Am I still on the air? Hold on a second
Ready
Today we're diving into one of the most intense
Misunderstood and powerful placements in the entire zodiac
Lilac and Scorpio in the 10th house. Let's be clear. This is not a cute little placement
This is the energy that walks into a room and changes the temperature, even if the person says nothing at all.
So let's break down the pieces first to understand what we're dealing with.
Lilith or Black Moon Lilith in astrology is the symbol of the part of us that refuses to be domesticated.
It's that raw edge, the hunger we were shamed for, the truth we were told to soften.
It shows where we've been projected onto, scapegoated, sexualized, demonized.
Or where we've had to reclaim a part of ourselves a society didn't want us to own.
Next, Scorpio.
Scorpio is the sign of intensity, secrecy, desire, transformation, death and rebirth,
psychological x-ray vision, and power dynamics Scorpio doesn't do small talk.
Scorpio does what's the real motive, what are you avoiding, what's the shadow behind that smile?
And finally, the 10th house.
This is your public life, your career, reputation, status, authority, legacy,
What you're known for, the role you play in the world and how the world judges you.
So, when you put all three together, what do you get?
A person whose public life is deeply intertwined with taboo themes, power, truth, intimacy, control, betrayal, exposure, and transformation.
This is the placement of someone who can become incredibly influential in the public eye, while also being profoundly misunderstood.
Because Lilith in the 10th house often marks someone who triggers authority structures just by existing, you might not even be trying to.
You simply exist in a way that exposes what's fake.
Now, let's talk about how this actually shows up in life.
The first major theme is what I call the Reputation Projection.
Lilith in the 10th house is famous for being a projection magnet.
People assume things about you, but assign motives to you.
They might sexualize your ambition, demonize your confidence, or take your very presence as a threat.
With Scorpia's influence, this projection intensifies.
People don't just assume you're ambitious, they assume you're ruthlessly strategic.
They don't just assume you're private, they assume you're hiding something dark.
And here's the brutal part.
Sometimes you get punished for what people imagine you are, not for what you actually did.
This can look like vicious workplace politics near campaigns, weird jealousy from bosses
or authority figures, or people constantly trying to humble you for having too much
power, charisma, intelligence, or influence.
The second theme is the Shadow CEO.
Willith and Scorpio in the 10th often creates someone who can operate behind the scenes
like a mastermind.
Even if you're a kind and ethical person, you are wired to understand systems.
You can read rooms, you can sense hidden agendas.
You know who is lying, who is posturing, and who is terrified underneath their confident exterior.
This gives you a natural talent for fields like crisis management, investigation, psychology, occult studies,
trauma healing, forensics, finance, strategy, or peer anything that involves high stakes and hidden information.
You're the person who can walk into chaos and calmly say,
But there's a price, you really get to be naive, you're simply not built for it.
This leads us to the third theme, authority wounds.
The 10th house is connected to all forms of authority bosses, institutions, even the
father archetype in some systems and the general idea of the world's rules.
With Lilith here, there's often a deep wound around authority.
Maybe you were told to be smaller, quieter, less intense, less sexual, less powerful.
In Scorpio, this story becomes about power and control.
You may have lived through moments where someone tried to dominate you professionally.
You've seen the dark side of authority up close, the manipulation, the coercion, the
hidden deals, the exploitation.
And because Scorpio learns through extremes, you might have had to burn down an old identity
That's why this placement is so often linked to reinvention.
People with this placement don't just change jobs.
They shapeshift.
Our fourth theme is the Taboo Calling.
Lilith Plus Scorpio can't help it, it's drawn to taboo truths like a magnet.
So in the 10th house, your public calling often involves making these taboo topics public
This could be exposing corruption, talking about sexuality without shame, confronting
abuse dynamics, challenging societal double standards, or pulling back the curtain on
a system that pretends it's clean and perfect.
This is why this placement can create such polarizing public figures.
Some people will admire you like you're a lighthouse in a storm.
Other people will hate you like you're a fundamental threat to their world.
You have to learn not to negotiate your truth for acceptance.
Now let's go into the shadow of the shadow.
Theme 5 is Power Image and the Trap.
Willowth in the tank can become obsessed with reputation because for you,
reputation becomes a survival mechanism.
If you've been misunderstood or scapegoated your whole life, you might over-correct by trying to control the narrative obsessively, and Scorpio loves control.
So the trap is becoming so strategic about your public image that you stop being emotionally free.
Another trap is using power as armor. Scorpio can weaponize distance. Lilith can weaponize defiance.
So if you've been hurt, you might adopt a persona that says, no one can touch me.
But your healing journey is about learning the difference between healthy privacy and
self-imposed isolation, because you don't actually want to be untouchable.
You want to be respected for who you truly are.
Next, Theme 6, Sexuality and Status.
This is where things can get weird, so I'll say it cleanly.
Lilith can symbolize sexuality, but more specifically, the part of sexuality that society tries to control, shame, or exploit.
In the 10th house, this can show up as your sexuality being entangled with your public identity, whether through how people perceive you, how you're treated, or what you're allowed to be in the public eye.
Scorpia adds a layer of magnetism and intensity, a kind of presence that people read as erotic
even when you're literally just sitting there drinking coffee.
This is why boundaries are non-negotiable with this placement.
Not because you're too much, but because other people will constantly try to define
you as a simple instead of a person.
Finally, we arrive at the highest expression of this placement.
Theme 7, The Redemption Ark.
When Lilith and Scorpio in the Tenth House is fully integrated, it becomes a public force
of transformation.
Not a motivational poster, a transformer.
Someone who tells the truth that actually heals, because it stops the lies.
Someone who's laid without playing nice with corruption.
Someone who can hold immense power without abusing it.
And that's why this placement is both so difficult and so destined for greatness.
So, let me give you some practical tells and medicine, because this placement needs a strategy.
If you have this placement, you should assume three things.
One, your career path won't be linear.
You're built for evolution, so expect major reinventions.
Two, people will project onto you.
Don't take every accusation personally.
Not everything is about you, some of it is about their own fear of intensity.
And three, you need a clean unshakable ethics code, Scorpio gives you power, Lilith gives
you an edge.
The only way this combination stays beautiful is if you commit to integrity, especially when
it would be easier to just retaliate.
And here are three medicine practices for this placement.
First, practice narrative control without paranoia.
Document your work, keep receipts, not because you're petty but because you are dealing with constant projection.
Second, choose your battles wisely. You don't have to expose everything and everyone.
Scorpio is surgical, strike only where it truly matters.
And third, build a public mission that can't be reduced to gossip.
When you are mission-led, smear campaigns don't stick as easily.
Because the core truth of Lilith and Scorpio in the 10th house is this, you are not here to be liked.
You're here to be real. You're not here to follow a script.
You're here to rewrite one, and the world will test you over and over by trying to shame you back into silence.
But your power is that you can turn shame into authority.
You can take the very parts of yourself you're told to hide and make them the foundation of your legacy.
When you stop fearing the spotlight, you become the very thing Scorpio always promises, the Phoenix with a job title.
Not just surviving, leading, thank you so much for watching.
If this resonated, don't forget to like, subscribe, and share with someone who needs to hear.
Please have it in my waller
Just do one of those
What's your God I just like that there's like $15
No, just try this cigar
Just a cigar, yeah, yeah
No, okay, well, thank you so much. Sorry. Well, never mind
Hebrew two dollars. I could edit if I could just get a cigar because I have enough alcohol psyche awakens. I
Thought I just looked at my thing and I had enough
You help me with the two dollars that'd be awesome, but let's pray once I get someone's gonna help me
This one yeah, one's fine
I mean look at it. Let's get as I put it. I just put it. It's like he awakens. Let me just take my cash up one sec
No way. I just checked it literally had
I have $1.71
The cold of psyche this is 10 of 10 p.m. They're about to close up a shop
They close the store right now
Always it's always in the last minute of me. I mean, just can you just be a little slow clean it up?
I'm just trying to wait. I mean the dollar 71 one
I have 171
It's too, I know I know I'm waiting. I'm waiting. He said he's gonna help me out
I'm about the guy's about to literally pull me out of the store
Divide and imagine me I'll say a prayer say a prayer for sake you right now
Thank you. Thank you
Good Lord, I was like I
Had I was like I was at 672 and I was like the drink and the thing was 694
And I was like can I give you the 25 cents tomorrow? There's no 20 cents
As a shit and I looked and it says savings $1.68 and so I was able to take a dollar for the savings
because you can only take a dollar at a time out of it and
Victory and literally the guy was looking at me like he was about to like the freaking throw me out of there
whoa
My life sometimes guys my life
It's like
It's crazy
I should have brought my coffee cup, but it's okay. I should have forgot it, but
Whoa guys, thank you. Thank you Hebrew
That was a close one
My life is crazy sometimes
It's like but you know what it's like this is my life the last minute the last literal last minute
9 59 close start the stores closed or actually 10
Even like a little bit after the last minute sometimes I
Get an extra minute
I get an angel
Whatever whatever
Readers background. I don't I don't know there's something
Some something looking out for me with sometimes human most of the times human angels, you know
We're angels working through humans
So I appreciate you
And I don't want to make you worry about me because you know I
Got help
Yeah, okay, can we just say a prayer for tricks my cat he hasn't been home in like 24 hours
I'm getting a little bit concerned not a little bit like a lot
She's not gone for this long if you're gonna say prayer
He's alive
He's safe. He gets home
It's happened before a couple times it's kind of like the
Part of like having outdoor cat. I'm sorry. I can't really see the chair and I'm really small phone. I
Will look at it when I get back
If we can say a prayer for tricks that you know he's okay. I appreciate you. I
don't know. I had a kind of a weird day. You know sometimes my faith is tested
a little bit. As long as I have like I think Jesus has something about it. If
you have like a mustard seed of faith
Miracles are possible, anything's possible.
Maybe I don't subscribe to exactly the religion as it is.
I was told, oh, well, you're not,
you know, you're not supposed to have Ganesha drawn
or I'm painted on a page.
You're supposed to have the statues and stuff
and all the stuff and then people are telling me
I'm practicing things wrong.
And then they say, well, I practice every religion,
blah, blah, blah.
I just mix a bit of this and that.
But if I knew that,
I'm sacrilegious, you know
It's called projection. They're asking me yesterday on a show. What's the definition of projection?
It's kind of like what it's always pretty much done to me, but
You know or it's like
But I'll
Sometimes I just act as a mirror
Just thank you guys to stay apart for tricks, that's the most important part actually, forget
about me.
Make sure my kitty cat is okay, I'm almost half a block away, almost there, I'll finish
I got everything I need to be comfortable, so I can't complain, you know
That would be there's plenty of people that don't have everything they need to be comfortable
And even like even like wealthy people can be unhappy people sometimes, you know, and so I
Don't care if my people call me a bum that I'm the biggest bum that you know, even my father was like
You look like a homeless person clean your nails
You know wash your wash your shirt like come come present yourself a little bit better and so
I'm I'm guys. I'm still still still learning, you know, it's kind of like what life is for me
It's like I came here to learn and that's until the day I die. I still I'll feel more to learn
I can study astrology or terror the rest of my life every day
I'll still more learn that I didn't learn but the biggest thing is like learning about myself
Love myself. Okay guys. I'll be right back with you. Okay. I love you. Okay, right back. I'll be right back on the house
made it that was fun it was fun you know because any mission complete complete
successfully it's about the journey not the destination sometimes right it got
close it got a little close whatever where's my charcoal yeah like we're gonna
Look how sad, look how sad Lola is.
I hope her trick is okay, look at her, hold on.
If you just didn't see her.
She has her head down, kinda sad.
She's kind of worrying to me, oh, look at this.
Look, she looks sad, because she misses, look at it.
Oh, he's okay. He'll be okay. Okay.
Too sad. So sad.
You can say a prayer, okay?
Every time, every time he's been
like a little long to come home,
I always will hear like
a little flap go and then he'll come running up the stairs
and be like meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
I know. Oh, baby, you see her? She's sad. That's why I kind of worry, oh, are you okay?
I never, she's never liked this, and that's why I've kind of worried a little bit more
than other times because a little bit longer. Lola, it's okay, come here. Lola.
And she's and she's sitting with Lenore too like she never is like really like likes Lenore very much
And they're like sitting next to each other like they're like the worried moms or my two female cats
And look here she hears like she thinks she hears the sound. It's like so sad. It's like
And she in tricks like you know
She she like
Didn't like oh shit. She's like didn't she as soon as he was big enough not to be breastfed. She saw breastfeeding him
Look at my phone, and I'll show you picture. Oh, no, and maybe tricks if I can find my pictures of tricks when she was born, too
he was like a little
You look like little mice when they're born kind of my Russian friend brought me Lenore one night because I had another black cat that
Ran away, and there are so many close calls like I went to this one lady's house
Because someone spotted this black cat in this lady's backyard
Thank you so much. I see that. Thank you so much. I
See thank you for the I see another person sent me something. Thank you so much. I love you. I'm gonna say it, but
I'll say this. Thank you very much
Thank you
It's my Russian friends like I'm getting on the bus today, and I'm going to Eleanor
She's like a and she's like I'm going I'm going to work and she sent me this photo of the bus
And I was like, whose legs are those?
And she just said LOL.
So I don't know exactly.
She sent me this Easter photo.
And that looks like tricks, too.
She's just moved into a house.
She loves cats, but she's kind of like the Elmira energy,
where she kind of wants to hug and kiss the cats.
But she's like look at the cats and look at this cat in the house this cat
And she's like this cat wants to snuggle with me like how beautiful this cat is
Beautiful cat, and she's like she's like look where I moved in and look it's full of cats
She was so excited
She's like I'm in heaven. She's like this is like right
But I'll show you
I'm Friday the 13th. She sent me this message
So, yeah, here's
This is one of my cats, I think this is a cat that came in the other day his name is marbles look how big he is
Yeah, big big oh no, that was Oliver that was Oliver Oliver was like
Fuck because I all over I had since the Glendale. That's Oliver. I've been to heck and
There's Oliver. He was there. She put a little red ribbon around his neck and he was a big fat cat
Who's the cool dude? I see he's still around. I see more. So this is Lenore when Lenore was like the first night
You know Lenore goes on my shoulder
Someone if someone found her she was like running around the parking lot
This cat lady like was looking for a black cat for me and this and she just appeared right and so if you put out
A trap in like she got Lenore. That's how little Lenore was look at Lenore now
But she was always like that and they're here. She is on my
My arm
The first night she was so happy. She's still so happy. You're so happy. Are you still so happy?
And I have a few more I think
This is my cat silly silly unfortunately the coyotes got silly unfortunately I was sad
And this is I had a cat Caleb and Caleb lives next door now
He has the air tag and then I had a cat named Toby and fortunately a car got Toby, but
You know there are dangers to having outdoor cats and stuff
It's sad and stuff and here's um, this was um, Lenore and Oliver
So she was a baby. We had these little cute collars and stuff
You're purring listen to this
You're purring. Yeah, it was she's so so precious. You're my babe, huh? My babe?
Hey, I
Think they're they're worried about
My baby you hear every purring
You know, I think there's like something really healing about cats purr
Oh my god, Lenore your butthole. Oh my god
Lenore
Something really really
Healing about a cat's purr and
I
Know Q's always showing his cat ginger. I had a cat named more too and more is also living nearby
Like these are just like I see these cats that like neighbors and stuff. Yeah
Was more and as she comes on my on the roof. I've seen her on the roof and stuff like next door
She's like does she found the one-to-one time they brought a this dog over his name is
What's his name?
Listen
Yeah, his name is bear. She brought this dog over named bear
Look at this video
Yeah
Three start
If I need to restart my stream, I'm on here when I was in Glendale when I had the trap house
Lady in red, huh?
That was my cat Alec she does you give me how like he was looking I
Love ginger cats. No, I don't need to restart. Okay, but that yeah, she's lady in red
She works it in and out right now look how skinny I am there
I'm fucking so skinny. I was guys I was kind of see if you think I'm skinny now. You should see me in my trap house and stuff. I
was fucking
skinny
Yeah, oh Lenore's butthole the cat form I need to restart. Yeah
Yeah, this was one time. She got me a manicure. My foot was like literally splitting apart and so she like to me to get a get a manicure
What? RG? She went to get manicure? I was skinny, huh? I was
What RG, but here's a picture of
Lenore when I got Lenore the first night here's her with Lenore
Hi Lenore
See it's her with Lenore
She's gorgeous. She's a Russian
Silly was like he was the cat, you know, he was but he was he always looked at the other cats
He loved looking at her cats
She I don't know but here and here's Lenore and I got Lenore the first night
She had her you see her eyes and she said it sat on my shoulder. Yeah, that's the Russian
That's my Russian friend and there's Lenore
Sitting on my back like she still does, you know
Beautiful cat
Yeah
That's oh, yeah, that's the brush and yep
You want to see I'll show some more pictures. She's I don't she doesn't really mind if I show pictures of her a
Few more pictures of her she's well, there's and here's Trixie. I just sent this picture of Trixie
Same prayer for Trixie. Let's hope he's right around. It's Trixie. He's just so comfy a little heart
I did some, like, AI of us together and stuff and went to dinner.
Pictures I sent her.
And she sent me this one.
I hope I didn't show too much or show that it's pretty beautiful show the boyfriend and stuff
But she was she didn't get like she doesn't make she she doesn't I don't think she minds went to Hutties
Look up the street and so recently I said I showed some pictures and stuff. There's one
Lenore, Lenore likes to be by the by the furnace like Lenore can like be by the furnace and stuff and it's like so hot
I'm like, how can you sit there? Are you like a hellcat cuz she's like, it's like hot
It's like a hot furnace that she just like says nice to it. There's the old man Rudy. There's some pictures of center
Mr. Trixie
Lenore when I come up why not come up, okay
Here's a cement that was sent outside my house
Like two thousand pounds of it
She's a firefighter of camp. She's really beautiful. I mean, it's like she's course. This is mini Manson's drawing of like tricks
That was my cat magic and that's one norm front. That's many Manson drew that
She can MK also you anytime. Hey
And I send her this picture me
Gene MK ultra you RG you think so
Yeah
What did I build? I built, you know, a
Frickin bunch of stats use a duck pond. Yeah, RG. Merry Christmas
Oh, that's sweet. Hold on
This meant she was in prison
I don't know how to say I think I guess Santa came to the jail or something
Santa came to the jail
She posted this little raccoon passed out in the liquor store bathroom
Racoon rocket broken the liquor store passed out in the bathroom. Okay
Thanksgiving pictures here's me in my playing the star right there
Happy Thanksgiving, right?
This is after she got out so I don't know if it's a hundred percent
She was maybe in a halfway house or something, but I do have pictures of her
Thanks, Santa happy Thanksgiving, huh?
She's right. Is that a turkey turkey dress?
She's not really the bronze chicken. I swear. Oh here. She isn't this is very Russian right there
Right
It was very like Russian
Peasant she got locked up from breaking into garages in my neighborhood
Yeah
She's a bad girl
This isn't this wasn't she was in women's jail. She didn't firefighter camp and stuff. She's really she's really awesome. She's really yeah
She's a little bit of a cat of Catwoman, right? But you know sometimes the
You know cat has nine lives. I think she broke into one too many garages. I don't have a sitar. I have like a um
I have a
Lear a lower liar
There you go
She looks more german than russian. Well, yeah a little bit german
Well, they're kind of like next to each other aren't they?
And then she see I got the I got the flannel shirt thing from her a little bit too
You know
Think they had a dog they had dogs in the jail. Hey, you know her name, Lace
And
How do you know her name because I think her name I said Elena
But this felt like that I made these a eyes of her for a video. I did
She's a firefighter and then she hits you she's the cats around her and she also in her chart
It says stuff about like lightning and fire and stuff. So
Push in Germany are kind of close, right? Oh, you said oh, yeah, but it's okay
Hopefully didn't see your whole name. I'm sorry shit
Roopy oopy
There are my Dicademy Awards.
I really didn't go to them, but...
That's not Lenore, but...
Docs, I'm gonna delete it, but hold on.
I would mess with her at your own peril, actually.
I don't know how they got this at the women's prison, but I don't know.
Thing that is, you're falling in love?
I've been friends with her since, like, 2008 and stuff.
Yeah.
Smoking, yeah.
She is.
I'm just taking pictures with somebody else.
I'll take it out. Yeah.
Think he's moving to California you're moving to California thing you're coming out
I don't know I forgot if I send it I think I send this one to her
Because it kind of looks like me a little bit that looked at me when I was wearing the vegan patriot wig
I think not the vegan patriot with the blonde wig, you know
Yeah, definitely
I know it's a lot of photos, but I just think she's gorgeous
She was doing women's firefighting kind of stuff the chainsaw
Oh, there's the last one, there you go.
I'm gonna restart the stream and just delete it,
but come back, join me in a little bit, okay?
I love you guys, come join me and we'll hang out,
have another drink, have another drink,
and hey, I love you guys.
Thank you, and thank you guys for everything, okay?
American Bag Girl, she was born in Russia,
she came out to America when she was like,
probably like 10 or 10 years old or something like that.
Ciao, I'll see you in a little bit,
come join me again, okay?
Love you guys. I love you tricks is gonna